easyroommate.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy

Personal data, or personal information as it is sometimes called, is data that relates to or is capable of identifying a living person. Our members privacy is very important to us and we do all we can to protect it. 

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to let you know the type of information we may gather about you, how we may use it, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of the information. 

## Information we collect and how we use it

We will collect information about you when you open an account, register with this website, place an order for services, or contact our Customer Service. The type of information we may collect includes your name, age, main activity, postal address, email address and phone number so that we can contact you if we need to. We may also collect information about how you use this website using cookies (Cookies are codes, made up of letters and numbers, which most internet sites will ask your computer to store to allow the site to distinguish you from other users.) 

We believe that the cookies you encounter on the Easyroommate site are either (i) necessary to perform the functions that members wish to use Easyroommate for, or (ii) are non-intrusive. 

To learn how to manage and remove cookies, please go to [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/). 

Please note, however, that if you set your browser to reject cookies you may not be able to use certain aspects of Easyroommate - and might not be able to use the service to its full extend. 

## Our sharing of information about you with others

We like to understand our members’ interests as well as we can, in order to personalise the offers we make to them through Easyroommate as much as possible. Therefore, we may provide personal data we hold about you as a member (such as your name and email address) to one or more third party bureaux which will match that data against other information. We always request these third party bureaux to keep data relating to you confidential. 

We will use the information they provide to us to target more accurately the offers that are made to you through Easyroommate. 

Your personal data may be disclosed if we, or an entity processing your data on our behalf, are compelled to do so by law, or receive a valid, legally-compliant request for its disclosure. 

## Security

We're committed to protecting your personal information. All information that you provide to us is stored on secure servers and access to this database is restricted internally. While no computer system is completely secure, we believe the measures we use reduce the likelihood of security problems to a level appropriate to the type of data involved. 

Access to your Account is password-protected for your privacy and security. While we do our best to protect your personal information you also must protect yourself. What does this mean? 

  * Keep your password or other access information secret.
  * Ensure no-one else uses your Easyroommate account while your machine is "signed in" to the Easyroommate site.
  * Make sure you sign out from your Account when not using it.

## Editing your Account and mailing settings

We like to keep in touch with our members so after you have signed up to Easyroommate we'll send you information or advices about features and services provided by us or our partners that we think will be of interest to you. 

Of course we know lots of emails can be annoying so we try to keep ours to a minimum. However, if you feel you're getting too many or would like more you can change the settings in your Account at any time. We have a one click unsubscribe policy, and each communication gives you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving similar future communications using a link at the bottom of the email. You can also review, change or correct your identity and email address information by signing into your Account and going to the My Account Settings menu. 

Please note there are some communications that are an integral part of the Easyroommate Service and cannot be opted-out of. This applies to – but not exclusively – email notification from other Easyroommate members. They can be brought to an end by de-activating your listing or profile, or by deleting your account. 

## Changes to this privacy statement

This Privacy Policy is correct as of 20/07/2016. Changes to our Privacy Policy may occur - if we make any changes to it we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it. 

## Registered details

14 Britannia Place, Bath Street, St Helier, Jersey, JE2 4SU 

If you have any further questions about this privacy policy you can contact Easyroommate on the details below. 

1st Floor, Regent House 1-4 Warwick Street, London, W1B 5LT.   
Email: [info@easyroommate.com](mailto:info@easyroommate.com)  
Phone: +44 2 07 758 3592
